http://www.drcrf.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
×
OUR LATEST DISCOVERIES
Enter your email below to sign up for our newsletters and updates.
Spam Control Text:
Please leave this field empty
SUBSCRIBE
AN EMAIL CONFIRMATION HAS BEEN SENT TO YOU
Thank you for subscribing.
Privacy Policy
The Damon Runyon Cancer Research Foundation (the “Foundation”) is committed to protecting the confidentiality of all information provided by its donors. The following sets forth the Foundation’s policies and procedures to meet this commitment.
Our commitment to privacy:
The Foundation will not share personal donor information with anyone outside the Foundation. Specifically, the Foundation will not sell, trade or share donors’ personal or contact information with any outside person or organization, nor send any mailings on behalf of any other organization.
Information maintained by the Foundation:
The information the Foundation maintains from its donors typically includes: names, addresses, telephone and fax numbers, email addresses, and donation amounts. This information is maintained in secure files and in a computer database which is protected by user identification and passwords. It is also protected against access from outside the Foundation.
Information obtained through the internet:
The Foundation receives donations through the internet. Any information provided in connection with web-based donations is passed through “Secure Socket Layers,” which encrypt the information as it is transferred to the Foundation.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes their IP Address, which is a unique number that every computer connected to the internet is assigned. With respect to cookies, we record session information and note what pages were accessed.
This privacy policy applies only to information collected by visiting our website directly. If you came to our website through another website or link to another website from the Foundation’s, please check the privacy policy pertaining to that site. The Foundation is not responsible for the privacy policies or content of any other websites.
Use of information maintained by the Foundation:
Personal donor information is used to maintain a record of all donations to the Foundation, to acknowledge any gifts made, and to communicate with donors in the future.
Requests to stop receiving communications from the Foundation:
Our donors always have the option of not receiving communications from the Foundation, either by mail, email or telephone. If you wish to stop receiving communications from the Foundation, please contact us and specify the types of communications you do not wish to receive either by emailing us at info@damonrunyon.org, calling us at 877-7CANCER or writing to us at:
Damon Runyon Cancer Research Foundation
One Exchange Plaza
55 Broadway, Suite 302
New York, NY 10006
Updating or changing personal information:
Anyone wishing to verify or update their personal information may contact the Foundation as indicated above. Please include your old and new information so we can make the necessary changes.
Commitment by vendors and consultants:
The Foundation engages outside consultants for various services and projects where they have access to our donor data. All consultants are required to agree in writing to maintain the confidentiality of any personal donor information reviewed during the course of the consultancy and comply with this privacy policy.
Revisions:
This policy may be revised in the future. Please check periodically to view any future changes.
Last updated 03/07/2018.
Stay connected. Sign up for our e-newsletter.
